<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Playstation &#8211; The Tech Show</title>
	<atom:link href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/tag/playstation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Wed, 15 Aug 2018 03:52:53 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0-alpha-43568</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sony Reveal PS5 Release Date</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/07/06/sony-reveal-ps5-release-date/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/07/06/sony-reveal-ps5-release-date/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 13:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playstation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playstation 4]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playstation 5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ps4]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ps5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sony]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1097</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The PS5 is definitely coming to living rooms around the world, Sony confirmed as they revealed a successor to the PS4 will be released.PlayStation exec Shawn Layden confirmed that Sony will release a PS5 during an interview with a German website. It had been rumoured that Sony might move away from the typical console release &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/07/06/sony-reveal-ps5-release-date/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Sony Reveal PS5 Release Date"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="text-description">The PS5 is definitely coming to living rooms around the world, Sony confirmed as they revealed a successor to the PS4 will be released.PlayStation exec Shawn Layden confirmed that Sony will release a PS5 during an interview with a German website.</p>
<p>It had been rumoured that Sony might move away from the typical console release model and instead have regular hardware updates like smartphones.</p>
<p>The mid-generation update of the PS4 with the PS4 Pro was seen by some as a sign of things to come.</p>
<p>However, Layden has come out to dispel those rumours &#8211; telling <a href="https://www.golem.de/news/shawn-layden-im-interview-sony-setzt-auf-echte-ps-5-statt-auf-konsolenevolution-1706-128536.html" target="_top" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">tech website Golem</a> that a PS5 “is coming”.</p>
<p>However, he said it will “probably be some time” before a PlayStation 5 is released.</p>
<p>The comments from Layden come soon after one industry expert claimed Sony were getting ready to release a PS5 as early as 2018.</p>
<p>Damian Thong had told The Wall Street Journal that Sony’s next numbered addition to the PlayStation line-up could release in the second half of 2018.</p>
<p>It may seem far-fetched for Sony to announced a PS5 while the PS4 is still doing so well for sales.</p>
</section>
<section class="text-description">The PS4 has also only been out for just coming up to four years, and the PS3 was seven years old when it was replaced by the PlayStation 4.However, there are is one important thing to bear in mind.</p>
<p>Thong has a track record of his PlayStation predictions coming true.</p>
<p>He correctly predicted that Sony would launch a PS4 Slim and a PS4 Pro (which he called PS4 4K) a few MONTHS before the consoles were announced.</p>
<p>If Sony were planning to release a PS5 in 2018, you would expect them to announce the console during the remainder of 2017.</p>
<p>There are a number of big events coming up in the gaming calendar where Sony could announce the PS5.</p>
<p>These events are the Tokyo Game Show in September and December’s PlayStation experience.</p>
<p>[amazon_link asins=&#8217;B071XTFP66,B071Z3JBVW,B06ZXQY1QJ&#8217; template=&#8217;ProductGrid&#8217; store=&#8217;thtesh0c-21&#8242; marketplace=&#8217;IN&#8217; link_id=&#8217;e65523cc-624e-11e7-bdad-895768fcbedd&#8217;]</p>
</section>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/07/06/sony-reveal-ps5-release-date/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sony Could Launch Next Gen Console In 2018</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/04/30/sony-could-launch-next-gen-console-in-2018/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/04/30/sony-could-launch-next-gen-console-in-2018/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2018]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playstation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sony]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=819</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[amazon_link asins=&#8217;B06WCZBYPV&#8217; template=&#8217;ProductGrid&#8217; store=&#8217;thtesh0c-21&#8242; marketplace=&#8217;IN&#8217; link_id=&#8217;30749113-2db7-11e7-a705-3da72cfca4ca&#8217;] &#160; According to Macquarie Capital Securities analyst Damian Thong Sony could release their next gen console in the second half of 2018. It has been observed that Damian Thong has been spot on with his previous predictions of Sony&#8217;s console releases. He predicted the release of the Sony Playstation 4 &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/04/30/sony-could-launch-next-gen-console-in-2018/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Sony Could Launch Next Gen Console In 2018"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[amazon_link asins=&#8217;B06WCZBYPV&#8217; template=&#8217;ProductGrid&#8217; store=&#8217;thtesh0c-21&#8242; marketplace=&#8217;IN&#8217; link_id=&#8217;30749113-2db7-11e7-a705-3da72cfca4ca&#8217;]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Macquarie Capital Securities analyst Damian Thong Sony could release their next gen console in the second half of 2018.</p>
<p>It has been observed that Damian Thong has been spot on with his previous predictions of Sony&#8217;s console releases. He predicted the release of the Sony Playstation 4 Pro and Slim.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s what he said</p>
<blockquote><p>Even without any insider knowledge, I can say with certainty that Sony <em>is </em>working on a new console, because these things take years to develop. But will we see it on shelves in 2018? I seriously doubt it. While announcing a new console could potentially be a way for Sony to disrupt the momentum Microsoft is building with Project Scorpio, the PlayStation 4 Pro is barely six months old right now and its official announcement isn’t even a year old. While consoles are moving toward a mobile phone-like model for updating and compatibility, fans would balk at a new console so soon.</p></blockquote>
<p>What do you think of this news? Let us know in the comments section below.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/04/30/sony-could-launch-next-gen-console-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
