<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Note 4 &#8211; The Tech Show</title>
	<atom:link href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/tag/note-4/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Wed, 15 Aug 2018 03:52:53 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0-alpha-43568</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Xiaomi Blames Extreme Physical Force For Redmi Note 4 Explosion</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/19/xiaomi-blames-extreme-physical-force-for-redmi-note-4-explosion/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/19/xiaomi-blames-extreme-physical-force-for-redmi-note-4-explosion/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Explosion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Note 4]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Redmi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xiaomi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1190</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you haven&#8217;t read our previous article covering the latest explosion of the Redmi Note 4 , here where you can read it: http://www.yourtechshow.com/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/ &#160; Xiaomi has released a preliminary report on the recent case of Redmi Note 4 explosion in East Godavari, Andhra Pradesh. The company said that it was able to procure the device &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/19/xiaomi-blames-extreme-physical-force-for-redmi-note-4-explosion/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Xiaomi Blames Extreme Physical Force For Redmi Note 4 Explosion"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you haven&#8217;t read our previous article covering the latest explosion of the Redmi Note 4 , here where you can read it:<a href="http://www.yourtechshow.com/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/"> http://www.yourtechshow.com/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xiaomi<span style="font-size: 1em;"> has released a preliminary report on the recent case of </span>Redmi<span style="font-size: 1em;"> Note 4 explosion in East Godavari, Andhra Pradesh. The company said that it was able to procure the device after a week of multiple conversations with the customer, who had claimed to be seriously injured due to the explosion.</span></p>
<p>“Upon first impressions of the damaged device, we can conclude that extreme external force was applied to the device, which led to the back cover and battery being bent and screen getting damaged. A detailed investigation has been launched to understand the exact cause of the damage,” Xiaomi said in a statement.</p>
<p>“We would like to request our customers to avoid opening the device, puncturing the battery or applying extreme physical force to the device. Further, do refrain from getting your smartphone repaired at unauthorized repair shops. Instead, if you find issues with your device, visit Xiaomi Authorized Service Centers or reach us directly on our hotline 1800 103 6286,” it further said.</p>
<p>Earlier, the owner of the smartphone, Bhavana Suryakiran claimed to have suffered serious injuries after his Redmi Note 4 unit exploded in his pocket. The owner had bought the smartphone from Flipkart three weeks ago. Bhavana had then said he was planning to take a legal action against Xiaomi and Flipkart for selling a ‘defective’ unit.</p>
<p>The latest incident comes days after a video showing an alleged Redmi Note 4 exploding, went viral. The video, however, was later turned to be a fake one.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/19/xiaomi-blames-extreme-physical-force-for-redmi-note-4-explosion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 Explodes</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/15/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/15/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Note 4]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Redmi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xiaomi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1187</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Xiaomi has launched an investigation after a Redmi Note 4 smartphone exploded in the pocket of a user in Ravulapalem in Andhra Pradesh’s East Godavari district. The owner of the smartphone, Bhavana Suryakiran reportedly suffered serious injuries due to the explosion. The smartphone company said it has contacted Suryakiran and is investigating the matter. “We &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/15/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Another Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 Explodes"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-1188" src="http://www.yourtechshow.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/538d1d48-81ae-11e7-aa81-8a4dce36eef3-300x169.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="169" /></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">Xiaomi has launched an investigation after a Redmi Note 4 smartphone exploded in the pocket of a user in Ravulapalem in Andhra Pradesh’s East Godavari district. The owner of the smartphone, Bhavana Suryakiran reportedly suffered serious injuries due to the explosion. The smartphone company said it has contacted Suryakiran and is investigating the matter.</span></p>
<p>“We take such matters seriously as customer safety is of utmost importance for Xiaomi. All of our devices go through stringent quality tests,” a Xiaomi spokesperson said in a statement, adding that they have contacted the customer and are in the process of procuring the damaged product to investigate the matter.</p>
<p><a href="http://english.sakshi.com/news/2017/08/13/redmi-note-4-explodes-in-owners-pocket-leaves-a-hole-in-his-thigh">Sakshi.com</a>, a Telugu news website, reported that the explosion took place when Suryakiran was riding a bike. A fire that broke out after the explosion could not be doused despite pouring water on his pants.</p>
<p>Suryakiran reportedly bought the smartphone from Flipkart 20 days ago. He added that he will move the court against Xiaomi for selling a ‘defective’ unit and seeking compensation for injuries sustained.</p>
<p>The incident comes weeks after a video showing an alleged Redmi Note 4 exploding, went viral. The video, however, later turned out to be a fake.</p>
<p>The company said after investigation, it found that a Redmi Note 4 belonging to Bangalore-based Arjun had exploded and the damage was caused due to a faulty third-party charger used by the customer.</p>
<p>“In addition, there were signs of physical damage on the phone as well. We advise our customers to only use Xiaomi authorised chargers and accessories,” the company had said.</p>
<p>Mobile phones exploding or catching fire is certainly not new. YouTube has a number of such videos. Just last year, Samsung faced a major crisis when it had to recall millions of<a href="http://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/dgca-bans-samsung-s-galaxy-note-7-phones-on-planes-over-fire-risk/story-RlVm6zZDNVC8Xk5o149htK.html">Galaxy Note 7</a> units after multiple reports of the smartphone catching fire.</p>
<p>Several airlines and airport authorities banned the use of the phone while travelling. According to Samsung’s probe, the Note 7 fires and explosions were caused due to faulty batteries.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/15/another-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-explodes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
