<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Divith Bajaj &#8211; The Tech Show</title>
	<atom:link href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/author/d_paaji/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Wed, 15 Aug 2018 03:52:53 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0-alpha-43568</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Apple’s HomePod delayed until next year</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/12/02/apples-homepod-delayed-until-next-year/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/12/02/apples-homepod-delayed-until-next-year/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 09:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1382</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Apple has delayed the release of its Homepod speaker until 2018. In a statement, Apple says that it needs more time to work on the HomePod. “We can&#8217;t wait for people to experience HomePod, Apple&#8217;s breakthrough wireless speaker for the home, but we need a little more time before it&#8217;s ready for our customers,” an &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/12/02/apples-homepod-delayed-until-next-year/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Apple’s HomePod delayed until next year"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/ii/l/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/TbOyAAT9S4oTedNxPFVB56or71g=/0x0:2040x1360/1400x933/filters:focal(857x517:1183x843):no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/57647653/v_8A0A9690.0.jpg" /></p>
<div class="lede__info credit-only"></div>
<div class="article__body">
<p>Apple has delayed the release of its Homepod speaker until 2018. In a statement, Apple says that it needs more time to work on the HomePod. “We can&#8217;t wait for people to experience HomePod, Apple&#8217;s breakthrough wireless speaker for the home, but we need a little more time before it&#8217;s ready for our customers,” an Apple spokesperson said. “We&#8217;ll start shipping in the US, UK and Australia in early 2018.&#8221;</p>
<p>The speaker was originally set to be released in December. Priced at $349, the HomePod is slated to take on higher-end sound systems like Sonos, as well as smart assistants like the Amazon Echo and Google Home.</p>
<p>The cylindrical speaker features a seven-speaker array of tweeters, a four-inch subwoofer, and a six-microphone array, which puts it right on par spec-wise with the best speakers in its price range, but where it may fall short is Siri, which isn’t really in the same class as Alexa or Google Assistant. That challenge is likely why Apple’s focus at the launch of the HomePod back at WWDC in June was music first and smart features second.</p>
<p>It’s unclear exactly why Apple had to push back the release of the HomePod, but pulling out of the holiday rush isn’t something that any company takes lightly. With no firm release date — early 2018 is vague at best — it could be a while before we actually see the HomePod on sale.</p>
<div class="c-related-list" data-cdata="{}" data-cid="site/related_list-1512155413_8814_8217">
<h3 class="c-related-list__headline p-alt-head">Also read</h3>
<p>http://www.yourtechshow.com/amazon-and-apple-beware/</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/12/02/apples-homepod-delayed-until-next-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Airtel deploys India&#8217;s first 5G capable technology</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/26/airtel-deploys-indias-first-5g-capable-technology/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/26/airtel-deploys-indias-first-5g-capable-technology/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1348</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel on Tuesday announced the deployment of India&#8217;s first state-of-the-art Massive Multiple-Input Multiple-Output (MIMO) technology which is a key enabler for 5G networks. Airtel is starting with the first round of deployment in Bangalore &#38; Kolkata and will expand to other parts of the country soon. Deployed as part of Airtel&#8217;s ongoing network transformation &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/26/airtel-deploys-indias-first-5g-capable-technology/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Airtel deploys India&#8217;s first 5G capable technology"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="col-lg-9 col-md-9 col-sm-9 col-xs-12 ybord">
<div class="row"><img title="Airtel deploys India's first 5G capable technology, will also help 4G users" src="http://media2.intoday.in/indiatoday/images/stories/rtr3b1pk_559_092617023532.jpg" alt="Airtel deploys India's first 5G capable technology, will also help 4G users" /></p>
<div id="impulseadcontainer" class="ImpulseAd"><ins></p>
<div id="beacon_d749e0fcb1"><img src="http://wtf2.forkcdn.com/www/delivery/lg.php?bannerid=0&amp;campaignid=0&amp;zoneid=883&amp;loc=http%3A%2F%2Findiatoday.intoday.in%2Ftechnology%2Fstory%2Fairtel-deploys-indias-first-5g-capable-technology-will-also-help-4g-users%2F1%2F1056184.html&amp;referer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.co.in%2F&amp;cb=d749e0fcb1" alt="" width="0" height="0" /></div>
<p></ins></div>
</div>
<div class="row"></div>
</div>
<div class="story_main_cont ad-blocker-ajax">
<p>Bharti Airtel on Tuesday announced the deployment of India&#8217;s first state-of-the-art Massive Multiple-Input Multiple-Output (MIMO) technology which is a key enabler for 5G networks. Airtel is starting with the first round of deployment in Bangalore &amp; Kolkata and will expand to other parts of the country soon.</p>
<p>Deployed as part of Airtel&#8217;s ongoing network transformation program, Project Leap, the MIMO technology will expand existing network capacity by five to seven times using the existing spectrum, thereby improving spectral efficiency, says the company.</p>
<p>Airtel has also claimed that customers will be able to experience two to three times superfast speeds on the existing 4G network. The data speeds will also be seamless and enable multiple users and multiple devices to work simultaneously without facing any congestion or experience issues especially at hotspot locations.</p>
<div id="zdt_3644892_1_wrapper"></div>
<p>Massive MIMO is a key enabler and foundation for technology revolutions to come. It is a pre-5G technology that will make the network future ready for meeting the data demand coming from digital revolution and data explosion in India. Customers can enjoy these faster data speeds on their existing 4G mobile devices without any upgrades or plan change. Massive MIMO deployment uses green technology and thus helps reduce carbon footprint.</p>
<p>India is fast striding towards exponential and unprecedented data growth.  Our latest deployment of Massive MIMO, will help us serve this demand and would also give an impetus to build a future ready network. The deployment gives us a strategic advantage to provide faster speeds and enhanced user experience for our customers, thereby translating into improved spectrum efficiency,&#8221; said Abhay Savargaonkar, director, Networks, Bharti Airtel.</p>
<p>Massive MIMO creates 3D beams both on horizontal and vertical planes towards users located within its coverage footprint. This helps in improving coverage and reducing interference across users in different beams, thereby improving signal quality (SINR) by 2-3dB. Serving multiple users by re-using same set of resource blocks (MU-MIMO) with improved signal quality helps in improving user experience, cell capacity and spectrum efficiency.  Airtel recently also announced a strategic partnership with Korean telecommunications service provider SK Telecom to leverage its expertise to build the most advanced telecom network in India. Under this partnership, Airtel and SKT will also collaborate on an on-going basis towards jointly building and enabling an ecosystem for the introduction of evolved technology standards of 5G, Network Functions Virtualisation (NFV), Software-defined Networking (SDN) and Internet of Things (IoT) in the Indian context.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/26/airtel-deploys-indias-first-5g-capable-technology/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>iOS 11 review</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/19/ios-11-review/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/19/ios-11-review/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 06:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1340</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[   What to do after you upgrade iOS 11 is available, officially, today. It&#8217;s coming to every iPhone and iPad made in the past few years, and chances are, you&#8217;re going to upgrade. When you install it on your iPhone, you&#8217;ll find that some things are very different than what you&#8217;re used to, but the &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/19/ios-11-review/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "iOS 11 review"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<h2 class="article__info-dek"><span style="font-size: 16px;">   What to do after you upgrade</span></h2>
</blockquote>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/-XYNTaj1T7Xe-ShOeMa15NbM1zs=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/56748791/dbohn_170625_1801_0018.0.0.jpg" /></p>
<div class="lede__info credit-only"></div>
<div class="article__body">
<p>iOS 11 is available, officially, today. It&#8217;s coming to every iPhone and iPad made in the past few years, and chances are, you&#8217;re going to upgrade. When you install it on your iPhone, you&#8217;ll find that some things are very different than what you&#8217;re used to, but the core of how you get around and experience the OS will be the same. For example: the Control Center is wildly different and notifications have changed slightly, but you still have that comfortable (and comforting) grid of apps on the home screen. A lot is new, but not so much that you can&#8217;t recognize it.</p>
<p>The iPad is a different story. That&#8217;s where Apple has made the most radical changes to the way you open and manage your apps. Apple has introduced an app dock that&#8217;s available no matter what you&#8217;re doing with a quick swipe up, so you can get to your most-important apps quicker. It&#8217;s also changed the way that multitasking works, giving you more flexibility with split-screen apps. And you can now drag and drop content between apps, a feature that takes some finger Jiu Jitsu, but is remarkably powerful once you get used to it.</p>
<p>Apple is the best at pushing these software updates out, and they almost always go off without a hitch. This year, more than others, you&#8217;ll be getting features that will make you want to upgrade.</p>
<p><strong>Features:-</strong></p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xEWT43cYOkrPTDMD57cxPiVwCpM=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9278671/jbareham_170917_2000_0124.jpg" /></p>
<h2>Customize the Control Center</h2>
<p>The first thing you&#8217;re going to want to dig into on iOS 11 is the all-new Control Center. It&#8217;s completely redesigned so that it sits on a single screen instead of on two or three swiping panels. It’s a little weird at first, with a wacky array of buttons and widgets. Some of them are simple button toggles, others are panels that you can force touch to expand for even more options.</p>
<p>Force touching the flashlight brings up a slider that lets you change its intensity. Force touching the networking panel brings up all your wireless radios and (praise be) a button to toggle your hot spot. One nice note: if you turn on airplane mode and then turn Bluetooth on again, that toggle &#8220;sticks.&#8221; So the next time you turn on airplane mode, your Bluetooth headphones won&#8217;t disconnect. Nice.</p>
<p>For the first time, Apple is providing a settings pane where you can customize which buttons do and don&#8217;t appear in Control Center, and you can reorder them as well. Apple is still not letting third-party developers put anything in here, but maybe next year it will.</p>
<p>In the meantime, there are a few panels that I&#8217;m really impressed with. There&#8217;s quick access to the Apple TV remote; if you have Control Center turned on for your lock screen, it might actually be more convenient than the real remote. I also think that the screen recording feature is super neat. It records a quick movie of whatever you&#8217;re doing on-screen. It seems like a feature custom-designed for reviewers and tech support, but it actually lets you do clever things like record gameplay or quickly grab a video clip.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m still mystified as to why Apple doesn&#8217;t put quick access to a Wi-Fi network selection screen somewhere in there, though. You still have to hunt through settings to change your Wi-Fi network or select a new one. I am glad to see that it&#8217;s easier to switch Bluetooth devices directly in Control Center, but I find the location (under the music widget) a little unintuitive.</p>
<h2>Learn how notifications work</h2>
<p>Apple and I have a very serious disagreement about notifications. I want them to be a place where I can quickly triage a ton of things. I want to get an overview of my day and take action on the stuff I care about while swiping away the stuff I don&#8217;t. I like to manage my notifications, and once they&#8217;re properly curated I get a ton of utility out of a notification pane. I can see what emails matter, I can respond to texts directly, I can dismiss stuff I don&#8217;t care about. I basically don&#8217;t even <em>need</em> the home screen.</p>
<p>Except doing all of that on iOS 11 feels like wading through chest-high mud.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/WSgaIeXY3X3JSui8TN-dpDu6CBE=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9272815/IMG_1831.PNG" /></p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s philosophy is that I&#8217;m trying way too hard. Notifications are flying in so fast and at such volume that it&#8217;s not worth trying to live your life in that screen. Instead, you should just let them flow by, pay attention to one or two that you care about, and ignore the rest. If you really care, you can hit a little X button to clear them all out at the end of the day.</p>
<p>Apple has made a few concessions to my way of thinking since the first betas of iOS 11 came out. You can swipe away notifications now, and there&#8217;s also that X button at the very top that you can force press to clear all. But Apple still adamantly refuses to borrow a bunch of the notification innovations Android brought, such as grouping notifications from a single app together and putting higher-priority notifications at the top. I also find that managing notification settings requires way too much bouncing around within the Settings app.</p>
<p>But the most fascinating thing about notifications on iOS 11 is that the shade you pull down from the top is <em>the same thing</em> as your lock screen. They look and operate exactly the same: down to swipe over to your camera and to your widget screen. It&#8217;s one fewer conceptual &#8220;Zone&#8221; to have to think about, and once you get used to it you&#8217;ll wonder why it wasn&#8217;t always that way. Especially with the iPhone X, your phone is basically always going to be unlocked when it&#8217;s in your hand, so it makes sense that the &#8220;lock screen&#8221; and the &#8220;notification screen&#8221; are collapsed into one unit.</p>
<p>One clever thing that you won&#8217;t see unless you get an iPhone X: iOS 11 can default to hiding the content of your notifications on the screen, as before. But as soon as it recognizes your face, it will show their contents on your lock screen.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/y1pcTKmUPShfKbeK_A5cADPDBck=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9272829/files_verge.jpg" /></p>
<h2>Dig around the Files app</h2>
<p>The next thing you should check out is the new Files app on iOS 11. It&#8217;s great. If you&#8217;re deep into the iCloud ecosystem, you&#8217;ll find all the files you&#8217;ve got stored on your other devices here — including what&#8217;s on your Mac&#8217;s desktop and documents folder.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s not that different from what was available before, but Apple is doing something new: giving top-level access to other, third-party cloud storage apps. Box, Dropbox, Google Drive, and OneDrive will all be available in the Files app. Right now, most of those just sort of link to their respective apps inside the Files app, but I hope and expect they&#8217;ll become &#8220;first class&#8221; citizens over time.</p>
<p>Whatever cloud service you use to store files (and at this point, you really should be using <em>something</em>), it&#8217;s worth stopping by the Files app to see if it&#8217;s working there. Chances are, it will be. The other reason to stop by the Files app is that it&#8217;s a good place to start playing around with another great iOS 11 feature: drag and drop.</p>
<h2>Learn how to use drag and drop</h2>
<p>On the iPhone, there are only two places where you can drag and drop stuff. The first is on the home screen, and it&#8217;s great. When you long-press (not force touch) an icon to go into &#8220;jiggly mode&#8221; to move stuff around, you can start dragging an icon — same as before. But now, you can tap other icons to add them to the &#8220;drag group,&#8221; which makes rearranging your home screen much easier.</p>
<p>The other place is within the Files app, where you can move multiple files between folders. Unfortunately, once you hit the home button, you&#8217;re all done dragging. Things are <em>much</em> more powerful on the iPad, where you can drag and drop a kajillion different things a kajillion different ways. You simply start dragging a file, photo, or a snippet of text on the iPad with one hand, but then use your <em>other</em> hand to start navigating the table to open the app you want to drag into.</p>
<p>More apps will need to gain support for drag and drop to make it truly useful on the iPad, but I&#8217;m a little disappointed that it&#8217;s not available on the iPhone. I get it: it already feels weird to be making these multi-app workflows happen on a big screen, so on a smaller screen it would probably feel like a mess.</p>
<p>Still, as I said in my preview, my favorite thing about iOS 11 is that it recognizes that its users are not so easily befuddled by complex user interfaces — and even if they are, the good ol&#8217; way of doing things is still available.</p>
<h2>Play with multitasking on the iPad</h2>
<p>Multitasking on the iPhone is basically unchanged. Multitasking on the iPad is a near-revelatory experience — at least for people who have been trying to do Real Work on the tablet for years now.</p>
<p>You can do split screen as before, but there&#8217;s more freedom to set your &#8220;skinny&#8221; app on either side. When you do split screen, those two apps get &#8220;paired&#8221; so they appear together in the multitasking view.</p>
<p>It goes way deeper than that, though. You can drag apps up from the dock into either side of a split screen. You can open a <em>third</em> app up in a &#8220;slide over&#8221; view that just sort of hangs out over your other apps, but it can dismissed and called back with a swipe over from the side of the screen. You can convert those slide-over apps into properly split-screen apps by carefully dragging a handle at the top of the window.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not as intuitive nor as simple <em>nor</em> as easy to manipulate as a traditional windowing system like you&#8217;ll get on a Mac, PC, or Chromebook. But it&#8217;s radically more powerful than what has ever been available on an iPad before. If it all feels too complex to you, you can mostly ignore it and just run one app at a time. But once you get a feel for it, you&#8217;ll find you can get much more done on an iPad than you could before.</p>
<h2>Give Siri another try</h2>
<p>The common knock on Siri is that people try it, it fails, and people stop trying it. Siri isn&#8217;t perfect, but it is much more capable than many give it credit for. Which is another way of saying: give it another shot, you might be surprised.</p>
<p>The big update you&#8217;ll notice right away is that Apple has tuned Siri so that its voice sounds much more natural and less computer-like. It&#8217;s just a little less grating to speak to your phone and have your phone speak back.</p>
<p>In terms of raw functionality, it&#8217;s hard to really pin specific features to iOS 11, since Apple updates Siri all the time on the server side. But two new things are worth trying. First, ask it to translate something for you. Siri can translate from English to Chinese, Spanish, French, German, or Italian at the start.</p>
<p>Second, you can dig into the General -&gt; Accessibility settings and toggle a switch that lets you type to Siri instead of talking. Unfortunately, unlike Google, you can&#8217;t have both speech and typing available at the same time. But if you absolutely hate talking to your phone, you now have the option to switch Siri to a keyboard interface.</p>
<h2>Take a screenshot</h2>
<p>In the past couple years, screenshots have gone from a niche thing a few people do to something everybody does, and so Apple has significantly changed how they work to match how we actually use them.</p>
<p>Now, when you take a screenshot, it throws a little thumbnail down into the lower-lefthand corner. From there, you can swipe it away to save it. But if you tap it, you get an entirely new little mini app. It lets you crop it and annotate it with a suite of little markers and pens and such. If you&#8217;re doing it on an iPad, you can use the Apple Pencil for more precise annotations.</p>
<p>From there, you can save it, delete it, or share it directly using iOS&#8217;s standard share sheet.</p>
<h2>Download some Augmented Reality apps</h2>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/iEk4-LY48YkRDX_n-qnoGAsJ7Qc=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9273525/The_Walking_Dead_Demo_Photo.png" /></p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s augmented reality system for the iPhone promises to be a blast. You&#8217;ll be able to measure your room, sure, but you&#8217;ll also be able to put a <em>T. rex</em> in it and play some incredible games on your coffee table.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s all built off something called ARKit, Apple&#8217;s system for allowing developers to map digital objects into physical space on your screen. It&#8217;s not a full-on virtual reality headset on your face, but it&#8217;s remarkably good at taking some basic understanding of surfaces it can see through the camera and putting stuff on them through your phone&#8217;s screen.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s much too early to know whether AR apps are going to be more than a fun trick to play around with for a few minutes before you forget about it — though that&#8217;s been the way many AR and VR things have gone. But Apple&#8217;s famous for getting developers on board with really good apps, we expect the same will be true in iOS 11.</p>
<h2>Turn Live Photos back on</h2>
<p>If you&#8217;ve turned off Live Photos on your iPhone because you didn&#8217;t really see the point, turn them back on. For one thing, Apple&#8217;s new system for encoding photos and video means they&#8217;re going to take up a lot less of your iPhone&#8217;s storage going forward. This new feature probably won&#8217;t get very much attention, but it&#8217;s a big deal because you&#8217;re going to be less likely to run out of space than you were before.</p>
<p>But mainly, there are neat new features that make Live Photos worth another look. You can still see the tiny little video that&#8217;s taken when you take a Live Photo by force pressing on the image. But now, you can actually <em>do</em> stuff with that little clip. When you&#8217;re looking at a photo, you can swipe up on it to bring up new options for your Live Photo, including making it loop, bounce back and forth through time, or show a &#8220;long exposure.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sharing these little clips is still a bit of a hassle, but it&#8217;s better than it was before. They get saved as MOV files, which should work on most social networks. If you want a GIF, there&#8217;s always Google&#8217;s Motion Stills app.</p>
<p>And if you are buying one of the newer iPhones, you&#8217;ll want to make sure you check out the new Portrait Lighting feature on the iPhone 8 Plus and iPhone X.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/96Y4yjDOWHxGrMU3BAaKuf35G7k=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9278677/jbareham_170917_2000_0148.jpg" /></p>
<div class="image-credit"></div>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/kRRCK9mtrcUcXf3FWBpJeqv7iQI=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9278681/jbareham_170917_2000_0140.jpg" /></p>
<div class="image-credit"></div>
<h2>Just look around at the new design</h2>
<p>You&#8217;ve probably been doing this already, but take a minute to look at the new design you&#8217;ll see all over the place. Apps now have these giant headers that make it easier to get a sense of what you&#8217;re looking at, so they work better on larger screens. Like any design change, the differences in iOS 11 are polarizing, but I generally like it better than before. Apple made a huge shift way back in iOS 7, but with iOS 11 it feels like everything&#8217;s been a little softened.</p>
<p>If you really want to get a sense of the vibe that Apple is going for (and, therefore, what many of the other apps you use are going to look like soon), take a tour through the Apple News app and especially the newly redesigned App Store.</p>
<p>Apple has basically turned the App Store into a tiny little magazine for apps. There&#8217;s a &#8220;Today&#8221; tab for featuring apps, complete with little articles about them. Games are finally separated out from utility apps, so the top charts aren&#8217;t completely dominated by them. You&#8217;ll see how buttons are more clearly defined as <em>buttons</em> instead of bare words floating in a white expanse.</p>
<p>For better or worse (and mostly for the better), the App Store is the clearest indication of where Apple&#8217;s software design is headed, so it&#8217;s worth your time to poke around in it for a bit. Plus, you know, that&#8217;s where the apps are. You should download some.</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px;"><strong>WRAPPING UP</strong></span></p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s real accomplishment with iOS 11 is evolving iOS to the point where the same basic OS works on iPads, iPhones, and iPhones with weirdly shaped screens. Heck, even the Apple TV technically is iOS underneath tvOS and it, too, is quite easy to understand.</p>
<p><strong>Credits for Images:James Bareham / The Verge</strong></p>
<blockquote><p>iOS11 Brings complexity but its worth it</p></blockquote>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/19/ios-11-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to pick between the iPhone X and iPhone 8</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/15/how-to-pick-between-the-iphone-x-and-iphone-8/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/15/how-to-pick-between-the-iphone-x-and-iphone-8/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 16:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1307</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Apple introduced three brand new iPhones on September 12th. Three! They include the iPhone 8 and 8 plus , which have faster processors and better cameras than last year’s iPhone 7 — and now you can charge them wirelessly. And then there&#8217;s a new iphone &#8216;, a $1,000 smartphone that Apple is basically trying to &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/15/how-to-pick-between-the-iphone-x-and-iphone-8/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "How to pick between the iPhone X and iPhone 8"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/nkJzKMz3WMzNQmi6Wbi-4eIBP-4=/0x0:2514x1676/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/56661493/Screen_Shot_2017_09_13_at_2.33.28_PM.0.png" /></p>
<div class="lede__info credit-only"></div>
<div class="article__body">
<p>Apple introduced three brand new iPhones on September 12th. Three! They include the iPhone 8 and 8 plus , which have faster processors and better cameras than last year’s iPhone 7 — and now you can charge them wirelessly. And then there&#8217;s a new iphone &#8216;, a $1,000 smartphone that Apple is basically trying to market as a gadget from the future that arrived a little early. It’s the first iPhone ever to have an OLED screen, and even better, that stunning display basically runs edge to edge. iPhone X comes with other radical changes like the removal of the home button in favor of a new feature Apple is calling Face ID, which scans your face to unlock your iPhone instead of the traditional Touch ID method still used on the iPhone 8 and 8 Plus.</p>
<p>So since there are three new iPhones arriving (almost) at once, you’ve probably been putting some thought into which is the best choice. For the purpose of this article, let’s go into it from the perspective of someone dead set on buying a new iPhone within the next couple months. You’ve ruled out the Pixel 2s and Note 8s of the world and have decided on Apple. Well, where do you go from there?</p>
<p><strong>Why you might want to buy the iPhone 8:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The iPhone 8 is the first iPhone to support wireless charging. Apple changed up the iPhone’s looks a bit this year with a glass back instead of just making the whole thing aluminum. So you’ll be able to plop the iPhone 8 down onto any compatible wireless charger and it’ll start juicing up. Many of the places where you’d find wireless chargers (like Starbucks and inside some newer cars) already support the same Qi technology as the iPhone, so it’ll just work.</li>
<li>It has the same powerful A11 Bionic processor as the iPhone X. That sounds like something from a <em>Mission: Impossible</em> movie, but all you really need to know is that it’s the fastest chip that Apple has ever put in an iPhone — and the iPhone 7 already felt plenty fast. This new chip is also optimized for all the cool augmented reality tricks that you might’ve seen demos of. Soon, those will make their way to actual apps and games in the App Store. All recent iPhones can do AR, but Apple claims the 8 and X have been “optimized” for it.</li>
<li>You get the same primary camera as what’s in both the iPhone 8 Plus and iPhone X. The 12-megapixel f/1.8 camera has a “larger and faster” sensor than the iPhone 7, says Apple, so if all you care about is having <em>one</em> good camera, this should be excellent. It’s got optical image stabilization and can record 4K video at 24, 30, or 60FPS — just like the other new phones.</li>
<li>The display supports Apple’s True Tone feature, which adjusts the screen’s appearance and color temperature so that it always looks pleasant and less blue / harsh to your eyes in a variety of lighting environments.</li>
<li>Unlike the iPhone 8 Plus, the regular iPhone 8 is still relatively easy to use in one hand. The iPhone X should be too, but it’s also hundreds of dollars more expensive.</li>
<li>iPhone 7 cases still fit.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Why you might not:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>It’s only got the one rear camera, so you lose out on Apple’s Portrait mode and the new Portrait Lighting feature, which can change the lighting of a subject’s face in your shot.</li>
<li>The 4.7-inch screen is smaller and lower-res (1334&#215;750) than the iPhone 8 Plus and iPhone X. If you like things to look big on your screen and get lost in YouTube videos or your Instagram feed, the iPhone 8’s display might not be ideal.</li>
<li>It has the smallest battery of the three new iPhones. Apple has promised users will experience “about the same” battery life as the iPhone 7, so you might find yourself buying a battery case.</li>
</ul>
<p>The iPhone 8 costs $699 for the 64GB model or $849 for 256GB.<br />
It comes in black, silver, or gold.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/w4R6xhUj-22fjQtG5GLvOUyuY-M=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9239803/Screen_Shot_2017_09_13_at_2.32.35_PM.png" /><strong>Why you might want to buy the iPhone 8 Plus:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Aside from their different displays and dimensions/weight — and those <em>are</em> important — the iPhone 8 Plus offers pretty much every single major new feature that the pricier $1,000 iPhone X does. It’s got the processor. It’s got the wireless charging. It’s got dual cameras on the back and can do the same new Portrait Lighting effects as the iPhone X. The 5.5-inch LCD screen has True Tone.</li>
<li>It has the familiarity of a home button and the versatility of Touch ID. Maybe you’re not convinced the iPhone X’s gestures and virtual home bar are really an upgrade. Plus, sometimes people just want to unlock their phone without having to look directly at it.</li>
<li>It has the best battery life of all three new models.</li>
<li>The 8 Plus’s display might be smaller diagonally than the iPhone X’s 5.8-inch screen, but it’s slightly <em>wider</em> because of their different aspect ratios. So some content — like your Instagram feed — will actually look larger on the Plus than on the X.</li>
<li>iPhone 7 Plus cases still fit.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Why you might not:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>This thing <em>feels</em> like a “Plus” phone more than ever before when compared to the all-screen competition from Samsung, LG, Essential, and now Apple’s top-tier iPhone X. Other smartphone designs are getting more efficient, but the iPhone 8 Plus remains just as unwieldy as its three predecessors.</li>
<li>Although the 5.5-inch 1080p LCD has superb color accuracy, it’s not going to be as vibrant or eye-catching as the iPhone X’s new OLED screen.</li>
<li>It’s not really all that much cheaper than the iPhone X. If you get a 256GB iPhone 8 Plus, you’re already inching very close to that $1,000 mark.</li>
</ul>
<p>The iPhone 8 Plus costs $799 for the 64GB model or $949 for 256GB.<br />
It comes in black, silver, or gold.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/W3BuGx5GNtT5193Hf6gAEYSiXKY=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9239819/Screen_Shot_2017_09_13_at_2.37.00_PM.png" /></p>
<p><strong>Why you might want to buy the iPhone X:</strong></p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3BNHyVyW6TI0UVC_BZ-N4UBn9fs=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9239851/Screen_Shot_2017_09_13_at_2.39.05_PM.png" /></p>
<ul>
<li>Visually, it’s Apple’s most impressive and futuristic iPhone design ever thanks to the 5.8-inch edge-to-edge OLED screen on the front and its stainless steel frame.</li>
<li>It’s a big screen in a small overall form factor. The iPhone X measures a bit bigger than the iPhone 8, but it’s nowhere near the dimensions of the iPhone 8 Plus. It should be fairly comfortable to use in one hand. And in that hand is pretty much all display.</li>
<li>The OLED screen has better contrast than the displays on iPhone 8 and 8 Plus, and it supports HDR video.</li>
<li>You can unlock your phone with your face. If you like being the first to try Apple’s latest technology, Face ID is the biggest adjustment that iPhone users will have to make in years.</li>
<li>Animoji and Portrait mode on the selfie camera. All of the sensors that make Face ID possible are also used for Animoji, which are moving emoji that mimic your facial expressions, and allow you to take portrait shots with blurred backgrounds (and Portrait Lighting) using the front-facing camera. Other iPhones can’t do that.</li>
<li>The telephoto portrait lens on the iPhone X’s dual-camera has a better aperture than the iPhone 8 Plus. (f/2.4 vs. f/2.8).</li>
<li>Both rear cameras have optical image stabilization, which should allow you to use the telephoto lens in darker conditions. On the iPhone 8 Plus, only the primary camera does.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Why you might not:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>It’s the most expensive iPhone ever.</li>
<li>There’s no home button or Touch ID. Unlocking your phone requires looking directly at it. Every time. Unless you want to go old school with the passcode.</li>
<li>Apple’s gestures for going back to the home screen and multitasking look somewhat awkward in early examples and demonstrations. At the most basic level, they’re definitely not as simple as just hitting a button with your thumb.</li>
<li>The notch that houses the front-facing camera and other sensors. It’s just kind of <em>there</em> all the time, and Apple is embracing that. That should be perfectly fine in apps, but the notch is likely to obscure content from time to time. We’ve already seen that it sticks out into videos if you play them full-screen in landscape orientation. Are you the kind of person who can ignore that? I’m not sure I am.</li>
<li>AppleCare+ is more expensive than for previous iPhones.</li>
<li>It doesn’t come out until November.</li>
</ul>
<p>The iPhone X costs $999 for the 64GB model or $1,149 for 256GB.<br />
It comes in black or silver.</p>
<p><img class="i-amphtml-fill-content i-amphtml-replaced-content" src="https://cdn-vox--cdn-com.cdn.ampproject.org/i/s/cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/M0Fm7GjlNZsPbwHOf6pmf0gaGlw=/1400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9240915/Screen_Shot_2017_09_13_at_4.21.15_PM.png" /></p>
<p><strong>What do all three new iPhone models have in common?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Same processor: A11 Bionic</li>
<li>Same primary 12-megapixel camera</li>
<li>Same 7-megapixel selfie camera</li>
<li>Same video recording capabilities: 4K at 60, 30, and 24FPS. 1080p slo-mo at 240FPS</li>
<li>Wireless charging</li>
<li>“The hardest glass ever in a smartphone, front and back.”</li>
<li>IP67 water and dust resistance</li>
<li>Same maximum screen brightness</li>
<li>3D Touch</li>
<li>Fast charging</li>
<li>64GB or 256GB storage options</li>
</ul>
<p>So if you’re already set on getting one of these new iPhones, for me it would come down to the iPhone 8 Plus and iPhone X. The iPhone 8 is a little too small for my big hands, and I need a larger screen. Picking an ultimate winner between those two might come down to the wire before preorders for the former kick off early Friday morning. The iPhone X’s OLED screen is beautiful, but a home button and Touch ID still feel somewhat critical to me — at least until I’ve handled the X firsthand and can judge the gestures and face recognition myself. The release date of iPhone 8 / 8 Plus and iPhone X are far enough apart that if you start off with one of the 8s and come to regret it, you’ve still got enough time to return it and hold out for the X.</p>
<p>Shame that Apple didn’t just put the home button and Touch ID on the back of the iPhone X, though. That would’ve been just about perfect.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/15/how-to-pick-between-the-iphone-x-and-iphone-8/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chinese developers pile in for the Next Big Thing in tech: voice-activated smart speakers</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/chinese-developers-pile-in-for-the-next-big-thing-in-tech-voice-activated-smart-speakers/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/chinese-developers-pile-in-for-the-next-big-thing-in-tech-voice-activated-smart-speakers/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 05:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1272</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#160; China’s tech companies are betting billions of research and development dollars that the next hit will be a successful version of the voice-activated home bot powered by artificial intelligence (AI), in the style of Apple’s HomePod, or Amazon’s Echo. What’s the Next Big Thing in technology, after the smartphone? China’s technology companies are betting &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/chinese-developers-pile-in-for-the-next-big-thing-in-tech-voice-activated-smart-speakers/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Chinese developers pile in for the Next Big Thing in tech: voice-activated smart speakers"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="article-images">
<div class="carousel__container bind-pswp article-carousel carousel-processed">
<div class="carousel__slide">
<div class="card image-pane">
<blockquote>
<div class="card-image"><img class="image" src="https://cdn2.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/styles/700x400/public/images/methode/2017/08/30/70e44744-8bbe-11e7-9f40-4d9615941c08_1280x720_105422.JPG?itok=USif1CiB" alt="A group of Chinese young people play on their mobile phone as they rest on a bench at a park in Beijing on November 7, 2013. Photo: AFP" data-src-hi-res="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/08/30/70e44744-8bbe-11e7-9f40-4d9615941c08_1280x720_105422.JPG" data-full-width="1280" data-full-height="720" /></div>
</blockquote>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>China’s tech companies are betting billions of research and development dollars that the next hit will be a successful version of the voice-activated home bot powered by artificial intelligence (AI), in the style of Apple’s HomePod, or Amazon’s Echo.</p>
<p>What’s the Next Big Thing in technology, after the smartphone?</p>
<p>China’s technology companies are betting billions of research and development dollars that the next hit will be a successful version of the voice-activated home bot powered by artificial intelligence (AI), in the style of Apple’s HomePod, or Amazon’s Echo.</p>
<p>Even though these products aren’t yet available in the most populous nation on earth &#8212; Apple’s HomePod is scheduled for worldwide release this autumn &#8212; more than 100 Chinese companies are already jumping into the fray to launch their version of the home bot.</p>
<p>“When we announced in April our plan to unveil our first smart speaker in the third quarter, we thought we would be one of China’s first,” said Li Zhifei, founder and chief executive of Mobvoi, a five-year old Chinese startup backed by Volkswagen and Google. “ We didn’t expect to see more than 100 companies entering the market in the past four months. We’ve now become one of the late movers.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/chinese-developers-pile-in-for-the-next-big-thing-in-tech-voice-activated-smart-speakers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon and Apple beware</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/amazon-and-apple-beware/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/amazon-and-apple-beware/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 03:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1266</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod New smart speakers including from Sony, Panasonic, Harman Kardon and Onkyo were revealed at Europe’s biggest consumer tech fair, with several using Google Assistant to help play music, control external devices and much more The runaway success of Amazon’s Echo smart speakers appears to &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/amazon-and-apple-beware/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Amazon and Apple beware"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod</h1>
<p class="article-header__subhead">New smart speakers including from Sony, Panasonic, Harman Kardon and Onkyo were revealed at Europe’s biggest consumer tech fair, with several using Google Assistant to help play music, control external devices and much more</p>
<p>The runaway success of Amazon’s Echo smart speakers appears to have triggered a rash of similar products. An estimated 10.7 million Echo units had been sold since its launch in late 2014 to May this year, according to US-based Consumer Intelligence Research Partners, a figure no doubt behind the number of rival products from many top brands at Europe’s biggest consumer tech fair, IFA, currently running in Berlin.</p>
<p>Using Alexa, Amazon’s cloud-based voice assistant, users can ask the Echo to play a particular song, make basic web searches, compile to-do lists, and even get traffic updates or weather forecasts. Google’s similar Home speaker uses Google Assistant, while Apple will sell its Siri-powered HomePod for about HK$3,500 (US$450) from December.</p>
<p>Apple should be worried. In Berlin, the likes of Panasonic, Sony, Harman Kardon, Onkyo, Libratone and Anker all revealed similar products that will be on the shelves before the HomePod.</p>
<p>Sony presented a splash-proof, 360-degree smart speaker complete with a clock display and the ability to communicate with other devices around the home. Called the LF-S50G, this Bluetooth speaker with NFC has the Google Assistant built in and can answer questions, as well as externally control Google’s Nest thermostat and Philips’ Hue connected light bulbs. However, perhaps the killer feature is that you can change music tracks by gesturing a hand left or right. Expect it to sell in November for around HK$2,000.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/46b9f31c-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="Panasonic’s SC-GA10 smart speaker. Photo: Panasonic" data-src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/46b9f31c-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
<div class="card-action"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Panasonic’s rectangular SC-GA10 speaker also has Google Assistant and is capable of streaming from Spotify, Google Play, Deezer and TuneIn Radio. Although it offers only 180-degree sound, two can be daisy-chained via Bluetooth to form a stereo sound stage, or even a multiroom music system.</p>
<p>The Harman Kardon Allure is arguably the most audiophile-attracting attempt so far, with a subwoofer inside an intriguingly transparent 360-degree smart speaker. It is due to sell in December for about HK$1,955.</p>
<div id="node-2109666" class="node-wrapper newsletter-widget-init lt_read_rull_tracked set-button" data-id="2109666" data-title="Amazon and Apple beware: smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod" data-url="/lifestyle/article/2109666/amazon-and-apple-beware-smart-speakers-star-ifa-2017-rival-echo-and" data-absolute-url="http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/article/2109666/amazon-and-apple-beware-smart-speakers-star-ifa-2017-rival-echo-and" data-published="4 Sep 2017" data-authors="Jamie Carter" data-sections="Lifestyle" data-topics="" data-email="mailto:?subject=SCMP:%20Amazon and Apple beware: smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod&amp;body=Amazon and Apple beware: smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod%0D%0DNew smart speakers including from Sony, Panasonic, Harman Kardon and Onkyo were revealed at Europe’s biggest consumer tech fair, with several using Google Assistant to help play music, control external devices and much more%0D%0D%0DRead more: http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/article/2109666/amazon-and-apple-beware-smart-speakers-star-ifa-2017-rival-echo-and" data-socialhead="Amazon and Apple beware: rival smart speakers star at IFA 2017" data-perp-article-type="" data-perp-topics="" data-perp-sections="94" data-ga="{&quot;dimension&quot;:{&quot;2&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:2,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;publishedDate&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;4 Sep 2017&quot;},&quot;3&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:3,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;authorName&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Jamie Carter&quot;},&quot;4&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:4,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;sections&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Lifestyle, Tech&quot;},&quot;8&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:8,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;headline&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Amazon and Apple beware: smart speakers star at IFA 2017 to rival Echo and HomePod&quot;},&quot;9&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:9,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;socialHeadline&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Amazon and Apple beware: rival smart speakers star at IFA 2017&quot;},&quot;11&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:11,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;nodeId&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;2109666&quot;},&quot;13&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:13,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;sponsoredStatus&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Editorial&quot;},&quot;15&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:15,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;writer&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;Contributor&quot;},&quot;16&quot;:{&quot;index&quot;:16,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;copyright&quot;,&quot;value&quot;:&quot;No&quot;}}}" data-menu-section="">
<div class="article hide-body body with-slideshow ">
<div class="node-col small-14 small-offset-1 columns">
<section class="node">
<div class="article-body clearfix processed processed-show-full">
<p>Also at IFA, Onkyo announced its Smart Speaker P3 for October, which uses DTS Play-Fi tech to stream high resolution music from Amazon Music, Tidal, Deezer and TuneIn.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn3.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/447bcc60-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="Attendees take a selfie outside Messe Berlin, the venue for IFA. Photo: Messe Berlin" data-src="https://cdn3.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/447bcc60-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
</div>
</div>
<p>Smart speakers are clearly the hottest new trend in consumer electronics, according to analysts.</p>
<p>“We think demand for assistants – especially in the home, and as they become more sophisticated – will make smart speakers significant, particularly within an audio-market context,” said Simon Bryant, associate director at analyst firm Futuresource Consulting.</p>
<p>He added that while the audio market is much smaller those for than those for televisions, appliances and smartphones, “smart speakers arguably have the most compatible feature set – speakers and microphones – so we expect it to remain significant, especially in terms of consumer usage and engagement.”</p>
<p>IFA also saw a clutch of new smartphones unveiled.</p>
<p>Though LG’s new <a href="http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/article/2109104/first-impressions-lg-v30-smartphone-light-slim-curvy-flexible-oled-display">V30 flagship phone</a> dominated, the event also saw the launch of the 5.2-inch Sony XZ1 and 4.6-inch Sony XZ1 Compact. TCL also showed off a special black edition of its 4.5-inch BlackBerry KeyOne handset.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/47c82422-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="Sony’s Xperia XA1 Plus smartphone, another of the models announced at IFA. Photo: Sony Mobile" data-src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/47c82422-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
<div class="card-action"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>If IFA is anything to go by, smartwatches appear to be a dwindling category. Fitbit’s Ionic was the biggest announcement; the brand’s first smartwatch will have a four-day battery life, act as a swim tracker and even be capable of making payments.</p>
<p>Samsung’s Gear Sport smartwatch can also make payments, but will be bought mostly for its extraordinarily lightweight design, weighing a mere 50g. It is also completely waterproof. However, with only a 1.2-inch display, it is also super small.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn4.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/473cd6ba-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="Phones from LG, BlackBerry, Alcatel and Sony were among those announced at IFA. Photo: Messe Berlin" data-src="https://cdn4.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/473cd6ba-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
<div class="card-action"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Far, far larger displays in the form of the latest televisions tend to dominate IFA’s vast exhibition halls every year, and though Berlin saw more brands embracing new OLED panels, there was something of an impasse.</p>
<p>The biggest TV brand in the world, Samsung, refuses to build OLED televisions, and though Sony announced the 77-inch A1 television, Bang &amp; Olufsen the 65-inch BeoVision Eclipse, and Panasonic its 77-inch EZ1002 – all 4K models – all are expensive niche products.</p>
<p>“Within the premium segment, the momentum behind OLED is gathering pace as high-end brands put their weight behind the technology,” Bryant said.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn4.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/461abacc-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="LG showed off its OLED TV ‘tunnel’ in Berlin. Photo: Messe Berlin" data-src="https://cdn4.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/461abacc-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
<div class="card-action"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>However, TCL, Hisense and Samsung are all pushing the rival QLED technology, which is essentially an effort to squeeze more performance out of ageing LCD display technology.</p>
<p>“While OLED was a focus for many, with vendors keen to inform on the benefits of the technology, LCD sets were still on display,” said Bryant, adding that even LG – which manufactures all the OLED panels used in televisions – was also promoting its conventional LCD TVs at IFA.</p>
<p>Perhaps a more important trend in Berlin was to do away with TVs altogether. LG’s short-throw projector, the Pro Beam HF85JA, can put a 100-inch image on a wall from just 12cm away, while Epson’s EH-LS100 achieves 130 inches from just 6cm away.</p>
<div class="card image-pane processed">
<div class="card-image">
<p><img class="image article-image lazy-loaded" src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/44171734-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" alt="LG’s ProBeam projector. Photo: LG" data-src="https://cdn1.i-scmp.com/sites/default/files/images/methode/2017/09/04/44171734-9125-11e7-b116-f4507ff9df92_1320x770_162314.JPG" data-src-hi-res="" data-full-width="" data-full-height="" /></p>
<div class="card-action"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p>Analysts have been predicting for years that projectors will one day bring a future of “screenless TVs”, and at IFA we may have had a glance at the truly bezel-less big picture of the future.</p>
<p>IFA Berlin ends on September 6.</p>
<p>Also read,</p>
<p>http://www.yourtechshow.com/chinese-develope…d-smart-speakers/</p>
</div>
</section>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/amazon-and-apple-beware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>New member to the voice assistant group.</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/new-member-to-the-voice-assistant-group/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/new-member-to-the-voice-assistant-group/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 16:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1262</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Chinese electronics giant Huawei on Saturday unveiled its first mobile personal assistant with artificial intelligence in Berlin, in hopes it will rival the dominance of Samsung&#8216;s Bixby and Apple&#8216;s Siri. &#8220;Smartphones are smart but they are not intelligent enough,&#8221; Richard Yu, chief executive of Huawei&#8217;s Consumer Business Group, said at this year&#8217;s IFA electronics fair. &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/new-member-to-the-voice-assistant-group/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "New member to the voice assistant group."</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span class="articleimg clearfix"><span class="agencymainimg"><img src="http://m.gadgetsnow.com/thumb/msid-60361359,width-400,resizemode-4/60361359.jpg?imglength=76396" align="left" /></span></span><span id="http://m.gadgetsnow.com/tech-news/chinas-huawei-unveils-mobile-ai-assistant-at-berlins-ifa/articleshow/60361367.cms"></span></p>
<div class="article-txt clearfix article-section">
<div class="clearfix">Chinese electronics giant <a class="topicslink track" href="http://www.gadgetsnow.com/brands/Huawei" data-track="Wap_AS|Topics_Inline|Huawei">Huawei</a> on Saturday unveiled its first mobile personal assistant with artificial intelligence in Berlin, in hopes it will rival the dominance of <a class="topicslink track" href="http://www.gadgetsnow.com/brands/Samsung" data-track="Wap_AS|Topics_Inline|Samsung">Samsung</a>&#8216;s <a class="topicslink track" href="http://m.gadgetsnow.com/topic/Bixby" data-track="Wap_AS|Topics_Inline|Bixby">Bixby</a> and <a class="topicslink track" href="http://www.gadgetsnow.com/brands/Apple" data-track="Wap_AS|Topics_Inline|Apple">Apple</a>&#8216;s <a class="topicslink track" href="http://m.gadgetsnow.com/topic/Siri" data-track="Wap_AS|Topics_Inline|Siri">Siri</a>.</p>
<p><strong>&#8220;Smartphones are smart but they are not intelligent enough,&#8221;</strong> Richard Yu, chief executive of Huawei&#8217;s Consumer Business Group, said at this year&#8217;s IFA electronics fair.</div>
<div></div>
<div>The mobile assistant, called Kirin 970, will systematically respond to three questions &#8212; <strong>&#8220;the most important combination,&#8221;</strong></div>
<div>Yu said:</div>
<blockquote>
<div>Where is the user?</div>
<div>Who are they and</div>
<div>What are they doing?</div>
</blockquote>
<div>Internet giants have been investing heavily in creating software to help machines think more like people, ideally acting as virtual assistants who get to know users and perhaps even anticipate needs and as smartphones and other electronic devices make greater use of artificial intelligence (AI), the digital assistants already pervasive in our lives are set to become more intuitive and play a bigger role in our homes, observers say.</div>
<div style="text-align: left;">
But unlike its competitors&#8217; virtual assistants, which collect and gather information in the internet cloud, the prowess of Huawei&#8217;s AI assistant lies in processing data on the smartphone, rather than in the cloud.</p>
<p>Yu did not offer details into what type of smartphones the chip will be installed in nor what price range those smartphones will fall into.</p></div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/04/new-member-to-the-voice-assistant-group/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t think of it as a watch</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/03/dont-think-of-it-as-a-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/03/dont-think-of-it-as-a-watch/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 07:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1256</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Samsung keeps the smartwatch alive Samsung has put its smartwatch on a diet in a bid to maintain dwindling market interest in the once-hot device category. Activity trackers don&#8217;t have the stigma that smartwatches do – so Samsung has disguised the watch as a Fitness Thing™. Its new Tizen-powered Gear Sport will go head to &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/03/dont-think-of-it-as-a-watch/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Don&#8217;t think of it as a watch"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><span style="font-size: 14px;">Samsung keeps the smartwatch alive</span></h1>
<div class="article_head"><img class="article_img" src="https://regmedia.co.uk/2017/08/31/samsung_sport_pair.jpg?x=442&amp;y=293&amp;crop=1" alt="" width="442" height="293" /></div>
<div id="body">
<p>Samsung has put its smartwatch on a diet in a bid to maintain dwindling market interest in the once-hot device category.</p>
<p>Activity trackers don&#8217;t have the stigma that smartwatches do – so Samsung has disguised the watch as a Fitness Thing<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />.</p>
<p>Its new Tizen-powered Gear Sport will go head to head with Fitbit&#8217;s new watch, and (probably) Apple&#8217;s third-generation Watch in the autumn shopping season. The Sport retains the characteristic rotating bezel from the Gear S series, and its 360&#215;360 display, and it&#8217;s a much less clunky package.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s 9g lighter and 42.9 x 44.6 x 11.6mm compared to the 49 x 46 x 12.9mm of the Gear S3. As the name suggests, it&#8217;s focused on fitness tracking and, more specifically, swimmers.</p>
<p>The usual 4GB of storage is inboard, a slightly smaller 300mAh battery than the Gear S3, it supports NFC payments via Samsung Pay, and will work with iPhones. It will compete with the make-or-break Fitbit Ionic watch, and Polar&#8217;s Wear-based fitness watch, both priced at around $300. The third Fitbit watch is no looker, but does boast its own OS, so has better battery life (Fitbit claims four days) and its own payment system, Fitbit Pay.</p>
<div class="CaptionedImage Left Border Float"><a href="https://regmedia.co.uk/2017/08/31/gear_sport_sideview_l.jpg"><img src="https://regmedia.co.uk/2017/08/31/gear_sport_sideview.jpg" alt="" width="518" height="512" /></a></div>
<p>Only Huawei and LG have stuck with Wear in a serious way, although boutique brands continue to dabble. Apple is expected to announce its new Watch in September.</p>
<p>The problem with Fitness Things<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is that the market may already be saturated – sales fell for the first time this year.</p>
<p>Samsung also unveiled a new version of its Fit Pro tracker.</p>
<p>Specs for both are <a href="https://news.samsung.com/global/samsungs-new-enhanced-wearables-gear-sport-gear-fit2-pro-gear-icon-x-combine-the-best-in-smart-living-fitness-and-health?utm_source=subkv" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/03/dont-think-of-it-as-a-watch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uber’s Pick for CEO, China’s Internet Crack Down and Attacks on Merkel</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/02/ubers-pick-for-ceo-chinas-internet-crack-down-and-attacks-on-merkel/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/02/ubers-pick-for-ceo-chinas-internet-crack-down-and-attacks-on-merkel/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1253</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Schulz Attacks Merkel as “Out of Touch” The German SPD election candidate is focusing on relations with the US as he tries to turn around his flagging election campaign. Editor’s Remarks: With only four weeks to go until the election, the Social Democrat Party (SPD) is trailing in the polls, with ratings of 22% against &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/02/ubers-pick-for-ceo-chinas-internet-crack-down-and-attacks-on-merkel/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Uber’s Pick for CEO, China’s Internet Crack Down and Attacks on Merkel"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Schulz Attacks Merkel as “Out of Touch”</h2>
<p><strong>The German SPD election candidate is focusing on relations with the US as he tries to turn around his flagging election campaign.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Editor’s Remarks:</strong> With only four weeks to go until the election, the Social Democrat Party (SPD) is trailing in the polls, with ratings of 22% against 38% for <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/merkels-cdu-set-key-state-victory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Angel Merkel’s Christian Democratic Union (CDU)</a>. Schulz has started to focus on traditional SPD anti-American and anti-nuclear weapon themes as he attempts to reach out to the approximate 40% of voters who are undecided and benefit from Germany’s strong disapproval of US President Trump. But the habitually pacifist German electorate has become more used to the country’s increased role in international affairs and seems comfortable with Merkel’s message of “stability and order.” The real race in this election is for third place. The CDU wants to avoid another “grand coalition” with the SPD and hopes that the pro-small business Free Democrats (FDP) can get enough votes to enter a CDU/CSU/FDP coalition.</p>
<h2>China Merges Power Giants</h2>
<p><strong>Power generator China Guodian will merge with coal producer Shenhua Group to create the world’s largest power company by capacity.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Editor’s Remarks:</strong> The merger has been approved by China’s State-Owned Asset Supervision and Administration Commission (SASAC) and will create a utility giant with over $270bn in assets. The new company, to be called National Energy Investment Corp, will have 225 gigawatts of installed capacity, making it the largest in the world, and will blend Shenhua’s coal supplies and coal-powered generating capacity with Guodian’s clean energy capacity. The mega-merger underlines the direction of the government’s state owned enterprise (SOE) reform process, where it is focused on industrial consolidation to reduce overcapacity and improve efficiency. The Shenhua-Guodian tie-up has been mooted for months, and analysts expect more of these mega-mergers as the government continues its SOE reforms.</p>
<h2>Samsung Tries to Move on</h2>
<p><strong>The South Korean electronics group announced a $7bn China investment after its vice-chair is jailed for five years for corruption.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Editor’s Remarks:</strong> While Samsung Electron ics has had a good year, generating record earnings and overtaking Intel as the world’s largest semiconductor company, its founding Lee family has not. The Group’s vice-chair and heir-apparent Lee Jae-yong has been sentenced to five years in prison for his part in a graft scandal involving ex-President Park Guen-hye, and there are worries of a “power vacuum” at South Korea’s largest company. The group has announced the China investment, to produce NAND flash memory chips that are used in smartphones, to build on its over 40% market share in the global NAND and DRAM semiconductor market. But following the conviction, Samsung could come under pressure from foreign shareholders, who own over 50% of Samsung Electronics, and may try to force a break-up and hostile takeovers of some of the Group’s businesses.</p>
<h2>China Outlaws Anonymous Posts</h2>
<p><strong>The country’s government is taking further steps in limiting internet freedom.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Editor’s Remarks:</strong> The new rules, announced by China’s top censor and set to be enforced on October 1st, are meant to eliminate posts by anonymous internet users. Internet companies and services providers will be responsible for ensuring users provide their real names when online and will also have to report illegal content to the authorities. This comes after the Chinese government passed <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/china-and-cybersecurity-2017-snapshot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">cybersecurity legislation</a> in June forcing tech companies to store data on onshore servers, which makes them more accessible to the authorities. The country also banned the use of VPNs recently, which made <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/apple-gives-chinese-government/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Apple drop its VPNs</a> from its China App Store. Facebook and Google are banned altogether in China, and players such as Apple need to decide which is the lesser evil – “bend” to the Chinese government and have access to the world’s largest market by number of potential users, or stick to their values and share the fate of some of its other American competitors.</p>
<div class="full-width-graph">
<div class="chart-inner"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-111543 lazy-loaded" src="https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-500x348.png" sizes="(max-width: 1450px) 100vw, 1450px" alt="" width="1450" height="1008" data-src="https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us.png" data-srcset="https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us.png 1450w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-300x209.png 300w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-768x534.png 768w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-1024x712.png 1024w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-500x348.png 500w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-672x467.png 672w, https://themarketmogul.com/file/2017/08/ch-vs-us-1038x722.png 1038w" /></p>
<h2>Uber Wooing the Head of Expedia</h2>
<p><strong>The ride-sharing company offered its top position to Dara Khosrowshahi, of Expedia.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Editor’s Remarks:</strong> The shortlist is said to have also included GE’s Jeff Immelt and HP’s Meg Whitman. Khosrowshahi is the current CEO of American travel company Expedia and would not come cheap. According to media reports, the <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/silicon-valley-overvalued/?hvid=4tBw7q" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Silicon Valley</a> company would have to pay the executive $160m in unvested stock options alone, should the deal be finalised. The move, however, would have one immediate short-term benefit: it could help bring an end to months of scandals and division that have engulfed Uber. The company’s former CEO and founder, Travis Kalanick, was <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/uber-boss-finally-resigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ousted back in June</a>. Khosrowshahi’s first line of business will probably be restoring investors confidence, especially considering the growing threats posed by competitors such as <a href="https://themarketmogul.com/didi-chuxing-chinese-uber/?hvid=1SJxJQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Didi </a>and Lyft, and the fact that Uber is still reliant on investor support as it continues to bleed cash.</p>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/09/02/ubers-pick-for-ceo-chinas-internet-crack-down-and-attacks-on-merkel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge OTA update rolling out with June security patch</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/06/25/galaxy-s6-and-s6-edge-ota-update-rolling-out-with-june-security-patch/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/06/25/galaxy-s6-and-s6-edge-ota-update-rolling-out-with-june-security-patch/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 08:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divith Bajaj]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1073</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is pushing out a new software update to Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge devices. The update installs the latest monthly security patch. Samsung Galaxy S6 is receiving the update as build number G920FXXS5EQF9 while the update with build number G925FXXS5EQF9 is being received by Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge. Alongwith the security patch for the &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/06/25/galaxy-s6-and-s6-edge-ota-update-rolling-out-with-june-security-patch/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge OTA update rolling out with June security patch"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Samsung is pushing out a new software update to Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge devices. The update installs the latest monthly security patch.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-1074" src="http://www.yourtechshow.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/galaxy-s6_blue-287x300.png" alt="" width="287" height="300" /></p>
<p>Samsung Galaxy S6 is receiving the update as build number <strong>G920FXXS5EQF9</strong> while the update with build number <strong>G925FXXS5EQF9</strong> is being received by Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge. Alongwith the security patch for the month of June, the firmware update also brings system enhancements and regular bug fixes.</p>
<p>The update is being seeded over the air to the mentioned Galaxy devices. As such, it may take a while to appear on your device. If waiting is not your thing, you can alternately check for it manually by heading to <em>Settings &gt; About device &gt; System update</em>.</p>
<p>However, before hitting the download button ensure that your Samsung smartphone is at least 50 percent charged. Also connect it to a WiFi network for seamless installation of the update.</p>
<p>Also read,</p>
<blockquote><p>http://www.yourtechshow.com/att-begins-rolling-out-june-security-patch-to-samsung-galaxy-note-4/</p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>[amazon_link asins=&#8217;B00UTGZ6GI,B00UTGZ0GO,B00U7YKSL0,B00VYKL5L8,B00UTGZD52&#8242; template=&#8217;ProductGrid&#8217; store=&#8217;thtesh0c-21&#8242; marketplace=&#8217;IN&#8217; link_id=&#8217;beb28e22-5983-11e7-95b2-9950d771c77f&#8217;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/06/25/galaxy-s6-and-s6-edge-ota-update-rolling-out-with-june-security-patch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
