<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Facebook &#8211; The Tech Show</title>
	<atom:link href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/tag/facebook/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Wed, 15 Aug 2018 03:52:53 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0-alpha-43568</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Facebook To Launch Chat Device With Facial Recognition</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/27/facebook-to-launch-chat-device-with-facial-recognition/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/27/facebook-to-launch-chat-device-with-facial-recognition/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facial Recognition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occulus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1234</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Social networking giant Facebook is reportedly working towards rolling out a video chat device that can recognise users&#8217; faces. The proposed device is said to be similar to the Amazon Echo Show, and will feature a camera, touchscreen and speakers, the Independent reported on Thursday. But the device has also raised fears among consumers that &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/27/facebook-to-launch-chat-device-with-facial-recognition/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Facebook To Launch Chat Device With Facial Recognition"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social networking giant Facebook is reportedly working towards rolling out a video chat device that can recognise users&#8217; faces.</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">The proposed device is said to be similar to the Amazon Echo Show, and will feature a camera, touchscreen and speakers, the Independent reported on Thursday.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">But the device has also raised fears among consumers that it could be used by the social network to spy on them, thereby casting doubt on whether the device would have all the features as intended when it is finally launched. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">Codenamed Project Aloha, the device is set to be released by Facebook in May 2018. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">However, it may hit the market under a new brand name, the report said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 1em;">The device is likely to be marketed as a tool to help old people communicate with their families and friends.</span></p>
<p>Aloha represents Facebook&#8217;s first serious foray into selling consumer hardware. The company&#8217;s Oculus subsidiary started selling the high-end Rift VR headset in January 2016, but Facebook hopes that Aloha will have more mass market appeal.</p>
<p>With a large touchscreen, speakers, and camera for making video calls, the device is intended to compete directly with the 299 dollar Amazon Prime show, which was released in June.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.facebook.com/images/fb_icon_325x325.png" /></p>
<p>While details about Aloha (including the name) may change before it sees the light of day, here&#8217;s what people familiar with the device told Business Insider abruptly about the device:</p>
<ul>
<li>Work on Aloha began after Facebook executives saw the success of Amazon&#8217;s first Echo, and now the Echo Show is seen internally as Aloha&#8217;s main competitor.</li>
<li>Aloha will be the first product to come out of Building 8, Facebook&#8217;s top-secret consumer hardware lab lead by ex-Darpa and Google exec Regina Dugan. Facebook recently put longtime VP Andrew Bosworth in charge of the company&#8217;s consumer hardware, including Oculus and Building 8.</li>
<li>The device will feature a large touchscreen along with a camera and speakers and be capable of recognizing people when they step into view. 13-inch and 15-inch versions of the device are in the works.</li>
<li>The magic of Aloha lies in its camera, which one source described as an &#8220;AI cameraman.&#8221; Facebook has hired top computer vision and AI experts to make the camera automatically frame shots and recognize objects in view. The device is intended to be used in the home and has been tested in kitchens, bedrooms, and living rooms.</li>
<li>Aloha will require either a Facebook or Messenger account to work, and will hook into the owner&#8217;s list of Facebook friends. That integration would let Aloha recommend that you start a video call with another Aloha owner if both of you are present, for example. One thing that is not yet clear is how Aloha will handle situations involving multiple users in a house with individual Facebook accounts.</li>
<li>The voice assistant Aloha runs on is loosely based on M, the AI chat bot assistant Facebook developed for Messenger. Opening up an audio version of M to commerce would allow Aloha owners to make purchases with their voice, as can be done with the Amazon Echo.</li>
<li>Facebook has looked at selling Aloha for as much as $499 but hasn&#8217;t landed on a final price point.</li>
<li>Aloha will be sold in stores and online. Facebook has considered selling Aloha through pop-up stores and inside existing retail stores like Best Buy. The plan is to sell the device in North America and Europe at first.</li>
<li>One hurdle Facebook has faced in building Aloha is consumer mistrust of Facebook protecting user privacy. The company conducted marketing studies for project Aloha and received overwhelming concern that Facebook would use the device to spy on users.</li>
<li>To assuage concerns about privacy, Facebook has considered creative ways to market Aloha, including pitching it as a device for letting the elderly easily communicate with their families.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/27/facebook-to-launch-chat-device-with-facial-recognition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revealed:Why Facebook And Instagram Were Down Today</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/26/revealedwhy-facebook-and-instagram-were-down-today/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/26/revealedwhy-facebook-and-instagram-were-down-today/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 19:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Instagram]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=1228</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Social media sites Facebook and Instagram appear to be down for some users this morning with some unable to post and others unable to access the sites entirely. Facebook users have reported issues accessing page mailboxes, uploading images, and posting updates, on both the mobile and web versions. Some users received messages saying that there &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/26/revealedwhy-facebook-and-instagram-were-down-today/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Revealed:Why Facebook And Instagram Were Down Today"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social media sites Facebook and Instagram appear to be down for some users this morning with some unable to post and others unable to access the sites entirely.</p>
<p>Facebook users have reported issues accessing page mailboxes, uploading images, and posting updates, on both the mobile and web versions. Some users received messages saying that there was a “temporary problem with this post,” or an issue with a URL, and to try again in a few minutes. Other users were greeted with a message that Facebook is down for “required maintenance.”</p>
<figure><img class="full alignright" title=" " src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xoEcFtzeC2PpYcZj0v9TOx5qSEM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9119845/DIKI_d7XoAEmpSv.jpg" data-src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xoEcFtzeC2PpYcZj0v9TOx5qSEM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9119845/DIKI_d7XoAEmpSv.jpg" data-original="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xoEcFtzeC2PpYcZj0v9TOx5qSEM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/9119845/DIKI_d7XoAEmpSv.jpg" data-sourced="yes" data-feedly-blocked="too small" data-sized="yes" data-presizing="presized.undefined too small" data-sizing="resized.full" /><cite>Image: <a href="https://twitter.com/An0nim0_o">An0nim0_o</a></cite></figure>
<p>Instagram users also found some issues when trying to access the site this morning:</p>
<p>The outage doesn’t appear to be affecting all users, and the cause for issues aren’t immediately clear. A Facebook spokesperson told <em>The Verge</em> in an email that “a technical issue,” was the cause of the issue, and that the company is “currently restoring service for everyone.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/08/26/revealedwhy-facebook-and-instagram-were-down-today/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Own Hologram Pyramid</title>
		<link>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/05/06/make-your-own-hologram-pyramid/</link>
		<comments>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/05/06/make-your-own-hologram-pyramid/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 10:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaditya Aurobindo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DIY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hologram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hologram cardboard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hologram pyramid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smartphone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.yourtechshow.com/?p=829</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;ve seen videos on Facebook and other social media sites of a hologram pyramid and wondered how it&#8217;s done then you&#8217;re at the right place. Here&#8217;s how you make your own hologram pyramid. Required Materials 0.5mm thick transparent acrylic/plastic sheet. (You can use plastic sheets used in packaging) Access to printer (if possible) Scissors &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/05/06/make-your-own-hologram-pyramid/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Make Your Own Hologram Pyramid"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve seen videos on Facebook and other social media sites of a hologram pyramid and wondered how it&#8217;s done then you&#8217;re at the right place. Here&#8217;s how you make your own hologram pyramid.</p>
<h3>Required Materials</h3>
<ol>
<li>0.5mm thick transparent acrylic/plastic sheet. (You can use plastic sheets used in packaging)</li>
<li>Access to printer (if possible)</li>
<li>Scissors</li>
<li>Cutting Knives</li>
<li>Clear cellotape</li>
<li>Ruler</li>
<li>Pen</li>
<li>Smartphone</li>
</ol>
<h3>Follow These Steps for Your Own DIY Hologram Pyramid</h3>
<p>1. Print out the template shown below on a sheet of A4 size paper.<a href="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/holoTemp-min.jpg"><img class="size-full wp-image-7908 aligncenter" src="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/holoTemp-min.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 412px) 100vw, 412px" srcset="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/holoTemp-min.jpg 412w, https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/holoTemp-min-300x278.jpg 300w" alt="diy hologram" width="412" height="382" data-cfsrc="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/holoTemp-min.jpg" /></a></p>
<p><strong>NOTE:</strong> If you do not have access to a printer, you can also make a template on your own. Draw a basic “Trapezoid” on a piece of paper using these dimensions. Parallel sides= 1cm, 6cm &amp; other two sides= 4.5cm each. You can always double or triple the dimensions in proportion to use on a larger display.</p>
<p>2. Trace out the shape on the plastic sheet using a ruler and pen. For the trapezoid template, trace out four similar outlines on the plastic sheet. Now carefully cut out the outlines with a cutting blade and ruler. Try to make your cuts as precise as possible for a perfect pyramid.</p>
<p>3. <strong>If you used the printout template:</strong>Score the red edges very lightly using a cutting blade. This will allow you to fold the edges better and form a pyramid shape. Stick the open edges of the sheet together using clear cellotape.</p>
<p><strong>If you used the trapezoid template:</strong> Join the four edges to form a pyramid shape. Stick them together.</p>
<p>Either way, in the end you will have a pyramid like the one shown below.</p>
<p><a href="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/plas-min.jpg"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-7883 size-full" src="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/plas-min.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" srcset="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/plas-min.jpg 400w, https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/plas-min-300x251.jpg 300w" alt="diy hologram " width="400" height="334" data-cfsrc="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/plas-min.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>4. That’s it! You have made yourself a hologram pyramid! All you have to do now is play a hologram video in your phone. Place the hologram pyramid in the middle of your screen like shown in the image below and enjoy the show. Don’t forget to switch off the lights in the room before you start playing the video.</p>
<p><a href="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Hologram-Pyramid-min.jpg"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-7873 size-full" src="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Hologram-Pyramid-min.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" srcset="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Hologram-Pyramid-min.jpg 450w, https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Hologram-Pyramid-min-300x200.jpg 300w" alt="diy hologram " width="450" height="300" data-cfsrc="https://301o583r8shhildde3s0vcnh-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/Hologram-Pyramid-min.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>You can find plenty of hologram videos on YouTube.</p>
<p>Alternatively if you&#8217;re lazy and want to buy one you can buy one from the link below</p>
<p>[amazon_link asins=&#8217;B06XYR375W&#8217; template=&#8217;ProductGrid&#8217; store=&#8217;thtesh0c-21&#8242; marketplace=&#8217;IN&#8217; link_id=&#8217;07dbd208-3248-11e7-a875-c9e118a82d62&#8242;]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://akshaybhopani.github.io/WordPress/2017/05/06/make-your-own-hologram-pyramid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
